When did you take
action towards
realizing the dream? Could have been a
very small thing, I don't know, but like
what was the kind of defining first step
that kind of set you on the actual path
to
realizing what you laid out? I took
action pretty immediately, but it took
me a year to quit my job. And I'll
define what the difference is. I took
action immediately by This might be
crazy. This was a Tim Ferriss
experiment. I really resonated with what
you wrote about
coming to terms with the worst possible
outcome. Mhm. And so I decided, I'm
going to train myself for the worst
possible outcome.
>> it. So I moved into a studio apartment
with a roommate.
I cut like like financially stripped
down I mean, I didn't have much anyways,
but stripped as much as I could to
simulate if if I'm truly failing at this
and having having to live in a Hollywood
apartment with a bunch of roommates, I'm
just going to get used to that. I'm
going to get used to it right now. I'm
going to cancel all of my memberships
and figure out how to stay healthy
with just myself just myself in this
small place. I am also going to commit
to working on my own stories after work
on the weekends because if I can't do it
now with stability, I I need to prove to
myself that I actually give a about
this really. And I did that for an
entire year.
Growing a little bit of a personal
savings, but also growing mental and
physical stamina towards
I'm already in still a place of safety,
of course, but I am in a situation where
I think I can handle this. I got this.
Like LinkedIn is up to date. Little
resume is up to date. I am so ready. I
have defined, prevent, and hopefully we
don't got to go to that third column
repair.
And so then a year later exactly, I quit
my job. And when I quit, I had
two months of videos backlogged ready to
go. Also legally for the record on my
own machine.
Not company resources.
All of that was ready to go.
And I knew what my first big project
would be, training with the stunt
doubles.
I had a shoot date ready. I had taken
you know, I only had like three months
of savings at that point. And I had had
allocated this is going to be for the
dream project. My first risk on my
channel. Nothing will touch that. The
rest is is for operating daily life
expenses. And I said, I got three months
to to make this work. And like you said,
you know, like we've been talking about,
sometimes you got to put your back
against the wall and go. I love this. So
>> [laughter]
>> So this is I feel like we were separated
at birth. So
>> [laughter]
>> So a few things. I'll I'll say number
one to try to I mean, not that I have
I'm not a paragon of self-awareness, but
I I will say that I for different
reasons have a certain like
hyper-vigilance focus on safety and
security, which might sound strange to
people listening, but
I'm always trying to risk mitigate,
right? I'm actually I don't view myself
as a big risk-taker.
I have done a few things that have ended
up with
>> [laughter]
>> me accumulating injuries that maybe in
retrospect shouldn't have done. But
broadly speaking, I'm always trying to
mitigate risk, which is underscores this
entire fear-setting exercise, right? Cuz
it's not just about convincing yourself,
it's also in my mind
completely intertwined with what you
did, which is
preparing
and training yourself and your
circumstances, right? So
when I flash back to starting my first
company, it's like, how did I start the
first company? I started my first
company during lunch hours, evenings,
and weekends basically while still doing
my other job and doing my other job
well. Mhm.
But I wanted to have a head start so
that I wasn't beginning from scratch
after quitting a job.